{
  "LevelId": 22,
  "Questions": [
    {
      "id": 220,
      "level_image": 4,
      "answer_text": "CHICKPEA",
      "question": "Protein-rich legume"
    },
    {
      "id": 221,
      "level_image": 4,
      "answer_text": "CHEEPING",
      "question": "Tiny bird sounds"
    },
    {
      "id": 222,
      "level_image": 4,
      "answer_text": "CHILDREN",
      "question": "Young offspring"
    },
    {
      "id": 223,
      "level_image": 4,
      "answer_text": "CHEERFUL",
      "question": "Full of joy"
    },
    {
      "id": 224,
      "level_image": 4,
      "answer_text": "CHUBBIER",
      "question": "More plump"
    },
    {
      "id": 225,
      "level_image": 4,
      "answer_text": "CHARRING",
      "question": "Burning slightly"
    },
    {
      "id": 226,
      "level_image": 4,
      "answer_text": "CHOIRBOY",
      "question": "Singing youth"
    },
    {
      "id": 227,
      "level_image": 4,
      "answer_text": "CHITCHAT",
      "question": "Casual talk"
    },
    {
      "id": 228,
      "level_image": 4,
      "answer_text": "PRAYING",
      "question": "Religious act"
    },
    {
      "id": 229,
      "level_image": 0,
      "answer_text": "CELEBRITY",
      "question": "Famous person"
    }
  ]
}